#### Contact

#(404) 5510283 (Work) angelica.brunache@amcconsul tingsolutionspc.com

www.linkedin.com/in/angelicabrunache-bsn-rn-4b3b8064 (LinkedIn) www.amcconsultingsolutionspc.com/ (Company)

#### Top Skills

Sales Microsoft Office Microsoft Word

# Angelica Brunache BSN RN

Director of Quality Assurance

Buford, Georgia

#### Summary

AMC Consulting Solutions is an Atlanta-based Health Care Consulting Firm that utilizes a total of over 35 years of clinical experience to aid in all your healthcare legal consulting needs. We offer a portfolio of professional registered nurses with extensive backgrounds in variety of specialties. Whatever your healthcare legal consulting needs are we make it happen.

### Experience

AMC Consulting Solutions
Director Of Quality Assurance
2019 - Present (1 year)

The devil is in the details. We at AMC Consulting know that many times the difference between winning and loosing a case resides in the details! We offer a team of clinically qualified and experienced nurses to find those details.

Emory Healthcare RN House Supervisor February 2020 - Present (5 months)

Clayton Eye Center
PACU/ Operating Room Nurse
July 2019 - February 2020 (8 months)

Premise Health
Staff Registered Nurse
December 2018 - July 2019 (8 months)
Greater Atlanta Area

Occupational Health Nurse

Emory Healthcare 4 years 8 months

Registered Nurse Emergency Department October 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 3 months) Page 1 of 2 Admin Secretary
May 2014 - October 2017 (3 years 6 months)

Emergency Room Technician September 2016 - September 2017 (1 year 1 month) Atlanta, Georgia

Vida-Flo USA Registered Nurse November 2017 - March 2018 (5 months) Greater Atlanta Area

## Education

Chamberlain University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2017)

Charleston Southern University
Bachelor of Science (BS), Psychology · (2010 - 2014)